Guide to the Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records
1938-2010
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections
3185
Office and Professional Employees International Union.$bLocal 8 (Seattle, Wash.)
371.06 cubic feet 367 boxes, 2 packages
Organizational records of a local union that represents over 4,000 members in health care, social services, insurance and office settings throughout Washington state
Local 8 represents clerical and office workers of a wide variety of businesses around Puget Sound. Name of parent body changed from Office Employes International Union to Office and Professional Employees International Union in 1966.
Organized into 16 accessions.
Accession No. 3185-001, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1938-1974
Accession No. 3185-002, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1972-1975
Accession No. 3185-003, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1944-1980
Accession No. 3185-004, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1978-1981
Accession No. 3185-005, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1980-1982
Accession No. 3185-006, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1976-1986
Accession No. 3185-007, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1979-1987
Accession No. 3185-008, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1982-1989
Accession No. 3185-009, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1989-1991
Accession No. 3185-010, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1992-1994
Accession No. 3185-011, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1995-1996
Accession No. 3185-012, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1995-1998
Accession No. 3185-013, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1999-2000
Accession No. 3185-014, Office and Professional Employees International union, Local 8 Records, 1995-2004
Accession No. 3185-015, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records, 2005- 2007
Accession No. 3185-016, Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records, 2008- 2010
Correspondence, disputes and grievances, negotiations, contract files, election files, case files, organizaing files, membership records, financial records, chronological files, legal documents, minutes, reports, convention files, newsletters, subject files, ephemera.
Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers restricted. Contact repository for details.
AFL-CIO.$bMaritime Trades Department; AFL-CIO.$bWashington State Labor Council; Central Labor Council of Seattle and Vicinity; Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound; Sea-Land Service, Inc. (Seattle, Wash.); Washington State Ferry Union Coalition; Washington (State).$bMarine Employees Commission; Office and Professional Employees International Union. Local 8 (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Office Employees International Union.$bLocal 8 (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Labor History; Washington (State); Seattle
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1938-1974; 3185-001; 19.25 cubic feet 19 boxes, 2 packages
  Correspondence, minutes, financial records, contract and negotiation files; 1938-1974 (bulk 1965-1973).
  Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
  Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers restricted. Contact repository for details.
  Received from OPEIU #8, June 4, 1981.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1972-1975; 3185-002; 12.00 cubic feet 12 boxes
  Correspondence, minutes, financial records, labor organizing files, negotiations, contracts and working agreements, arbitration and grievance files, elections, newsletters, legal documents, ephemera, subject series; 1972-1975 (bulk 1974-1975).
  Received from OPEIU #8, January 14, 1983.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1944-1980; 3185-003; 18.00 cubic feet 18 boxes
  Correspondence, minutes, newsletters, organizing files, grievances, negotiations, (1973-1980), financial records (1944-1945, 1971-1978); 1944-1980.
  Received from OPEIU #8, June 20, 1986.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1978-1981; 3185-004; 8.00 cubic feet 8 boxes
  Correspondence, organizing files, financial records, newsletters, elections, subject series; 1978-1981 (bulk 1979-1980).
  Received from OPEIU #8, July 14, 1988.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1980-1982; 3185-005; 7.00 cubic feet 7 boxes
  Correspondence, minutes, financial records, reports, newsletters, elections, conferences and conventions, subject series; 1980-1982 (bulk 1981-1982).
  Received from OPEIU #8, March 16, 1990.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1976-1986; 3185-006; 11.42 cubic feet 12 boxes
  Membership records, miscellaneous correspondence, contract negotiations, financial records, grievance files, and related records, 1976-1986.
  Includes records of the Sea-Land trial (1979), Sea-Land strike and trial (1982-1983), and correspondence and other documentation on an internal leadership dispute (1984-1985).
  Received from OPEIU #8, July 19, 1993.
  - Organizational Records
    - General Correspondence, 1984-86, undated (Box 1)
    - Negotiations, Employer Correspondence & Grievances, 1983-86 (Box 1-6)
    - Negotiations, Employer Correspondence & Grievances - Trade Section, 1983-86 (Box 6)
    - Case Files 7
      - Sea-Land, 1979-86
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-85
    - Grievances (including Margaret Bartholomeaux Trial), 1976-83 (Box 8)
    - Subject Series
      - Pension & Retirement, 1983-86 (Box 8-9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-89
    - Newsletters, 1984-86
    - Elections, 1982-85 (Box 10)
    - Conferences & Seminars, 1984-86
    - Financial Records, 1984-85
    - Unsorted
  - American Federation Of Labor - Congress Of Inustrial Organizations. Maritime Trades Department, 1983-86
  - Central Labor Council, King County (afl-cio), 1983-87 (Box 11)
  - Office And Professional Employees International Union, 1984-86
  - OPEIU. Local 8. Seattle. Executive Board, 1986
  - Washington. Marine Employees Commission, 1984-85
  - Washington State Ferry Coalition, 1982-83
  - Washington State Labor Council, 1983-86 (Box 11-12)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1979-1987; 3185-007; 35.00 cubic feet 35 boxes
  Correspondence, disputes and grievances, negotiations, case file, per capita reports, financial records, conferences and conventions; 1979-1987.
  Received from OPEIU #8, April 4, 1994.
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1982-1989; 3185-008; 19.42 cubic ft. 20 boxes
  General correspondence, organizing files, grievances, negotiations, election and other files related to affairs of the union; 1982-1989 (bulk 1987-1989).
  Received from OPEIU #8, June 2, 1997.
  - Organizing Files, 1982-89 (Box 1)
  - Organizing Files, 1988-89 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988
  - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3-4)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5-7)
  - Disputes And Grievances, 1987 (Box 7-8)
    Restricted.
  - Disputes And Grievances, 1988 (Box 8-9)
  - Disputes And Grievances, 1989 (Box 9-10)
  - Negotiations (IAM751 - Sheet Metal), 1987 (Box 11)
  - Negotiations (Speea - Webster), 1987 (Box 12)
  - Negotiations (Welfare - Willapa), 1987 (Box 13)
  - Negotiations (A - G), 1988
  - Negotiations (G - T), 1988 (Box 14)
  - Negotiations (U - W), 1988 (Box 15)
  - Negotiations (A - S), 1989 (Box 16)
  - Negotiations (S - W), 1989 (Box 17)
  - International Correspondence, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Washington Office Employees Security Fund, 1988
  - Western States Pension Information, 1988
  - Supplemental Pension, 1988
  - Washington State Labor Council Convention, 1988
  - International Reports, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Washington Office Employees Security Fund, 1989
  - Western States Pension Information, 1989
  - Supplemental Pension, 1989
  - Executive Board Correspondence, 1989
  - General Election Information, 1989 (Box 19-20)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1989-1991; 3185-009; 33.00 cubic feet 33 boxes
  General correspondence, negotiations, disputes, grievances, Executive Board election file, and other files related to affairs of the union; 1989-1991 (bulk 1990-1991).
  Received from OPEIU #8, September 27, 1999.
  - Organizational Records
    - General Correspondence (A-I), 1990 (Box 1)
    - General Correspondence (K-S), 1990 (Box 2)
    - General Correspondence (T-W), 1990 (Box 3)
    - General Correspondence (A-G), 1991 (Box 4)
    - General Correspondence (G-S), 1991 (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence (S-W), 1991 (Box 6)
    - General Correspondence (W-Z), 1991 (Box 7)
    - Negotiations (A-G), 1990 (Box 8)
    - Negotiations (G-H), 1990 (Box 9)
    - Negotiations (H-S), 1990 (Box 10)
    - Negotiations (S-Z), 1990 (Box 11)
    - Negotiations (A-H), 1991 (Box 12)
    - Negotiations (I-Z), 1991 (Box 13)
    - Old Signed Labor Agreements No Longer Under OPEIU Jurisdiction, undated (Box 14)
    - Disputes And Grievances (A-I), 1990 (Box 15)
    - Disputes And Grievances (J-R), 1990 (Box 16)
    - Disputes And Grievances (S-Z), 1990 (Box 17)
    - Disputes And Grievances (A-F), 1991 (Box 18)
    - Disputes And Grievances (G-N), 1991 (Box 19)
    - Disputes And Grievances (O-Z), 1991 (Box 20)
    - Kathy Whitaker Grievances, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
    - King County Medical Blue Shield Decertification Campaign And Boycott, 1990 (Box 22-25)
      - Miscellaneous Lobbying and Fundraising, 1989 (Box 25)
      - King County Medical Pins, undated (Box 26)
      - American Passage Lobbying and Fundraising, undated
      - Catholic Community Services -- Home Care Workers Organizing, 1989-1990
  - Catholic Community Services -- Home Care Workers Organizing (box 27 Also Contains Two Vhs Videotapes), 1989 (Box 27-28)
  - American Passage Union Campaign, 1989-1990 (Box 28-29)
    - International Supplemental Pension, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Washington Office Employees Security Fund, 1990
    - Western States Pension Fund, 1990
    - International Supplemental Pension, 1991 (Box 31)
    - Washington Office Employees Security Fund, 1991
    - Western States Pension Fund, 1991
    - International Association Of Machinists And Aerospace Workers. District Lodge 751., 1991 (Box 32)
    - Special Executive Board Election, 1990
    - Miscellaneous Files, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1992-1994; 3185-010; 29.00 cubic feet 29 boxes
  General correspondence, grievance files, negotiation files, and miscellaneous other files; 1992-1994.
  Received from OPEIU #8, January 23, 2003.
  - Correspondence
    - General Correspondence (A - L), 1992 (Box 1)
    - General Correspondence (M - V), 1992 (Box 2)
    - General Correspondence (V - Z), 1992 (Box 3)
    - General Correspondence (A - G), 1993
    - General Correspondence (F - I), 1993 (Box 4)
    - General Correspondence (I - V), 1993 (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence (W), 1993 (Box 6)
    - General Correspondence (A - G), 1994
    - General Correspondence (G - S), 1994 (Box 7)
    - General Correspondence (S - W), 1994 (Box 8)
    - International Correspondence, 1992-93 (Box 9)
      - Supplemental Pension
      - Washington Office
      - Employees Security Fund
      - Western States Pension
      - Local 8 Top Drawer
      - Western states pension correspondence
      - Western States Pension Correspondence
    - International Correspondence, 1993-94 (Box 10)
      - Western States Pension Correspondence
    - International Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11)
      - Supplemental Pension
      - Washington Office Employees Security Fund
      - Western States Pension
  - Election Files (Box 11-12)
    - Vice President Election, 1992
    - General Election, 1993
    - Disputes And Grievances
      - Disputes and Grievances (A - P), 1992 (Box 13)
      - Disputes and Grievances (R - W), 1992 (Box 14)
      - Disputes and Grievances (W - Y), 1992 (Box 15)
      - Disputes and Grievances (A - J), 1993
      - Disputes and Grievances (J - Z), 1993 (Box 16)
      - Disputes and Grievances (A - J), 1994 (Box 17)
      - Disputes and Grievances (K - W), 1994 (Box 18)
    - Negotiations
      - Negotiations (A - Group Health), 1992 (Box 19)
      - Negotiations (Group Health - Plumbers Local 265), 1992 (Box 20)
      - Negotiations (Sea Mar - Trade Section), 1992 (Box 21)
      - Negotiations (TCI - Willapa), 1992 (Box 22)
      - Negotiations (A - E), 1993
      - Negotiations (E - P), 1993 (Box 23)
      - Negotiations (R - S), 1993 (Box 24)
      - Negotiations (S - W), 1993 (Box 25)
      - Negotiations (Wa - We), 1993 (Box 26)
      - Negotiations (A - O), 1994 (Box 27)
      - Negotiations (P - T), 1994 (Box 28)
      - Negotiations (Trade Section - W), 1994 (Box 29)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1995-1996; 3185-011; 25.00 cubic feet 25 boxes
  General correspondence, minutes, reports, newsletters, disputes, grievances, negotiations, election and other files related to affairs of the union; 1995-1996.
  Received from OPEIU #8, April 4, 2004.
  - Correspondence
    - General Correspondence (a-m), 1995 (Box 1)
    - General Correspondence (m-t), 1995 (Box 2)
    - General Correspondence (t-w), 1995 (Box 3)
    - General Correspondence (a-f), 1996 (Box 4)
    - General Correspondence (ghc), 1996 (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence (h-s), 1996 (Box 6)
    - General Correspondence (s-w), 1996 (Box 7)
    - General Correspondence (w), 1996 (Box 8)
    - International Correspondence, 1996
      - Supplemental Pension
      - Puget Sound Benefit Trust
    - International Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9)
      - Supplemental Pension
      - Puget Sound Benefits Trust
  - Miscellaneous Office Files, 1996
    - Business Representative Reports (Box 10)
    - Newsletters
    - Executive Board Correspondence
    - Pdc Reports
  - Personnel Files
    - Dispute And Grievance Files
      - Disputes and Grievances (A-M), 1995 (Box 11)
      - Disputes and Grievances (M-S), 1995 (Box 12)
      - Disputes and Grievances (S-W), 1995 (Box 13)
      - Disputes and Grievances (A-C), 1996 (Box 14)
      - Disputes and Grievances (D-P), 1996 (Box 15)
      - Disputes and Grievances (P-W), 1996 (Box 16)
    - Negotiation Files
      - Negotiations (A-C), 1995 (Box 17)
      - Negotiations (CCAP-CWA), 1995 (Box 18)
      - Negotiations (GHC), 1995 (Box 19)
      - Negotiations (GHC), 1995 (Box 20)
      - Negotiations (N-S), 1995 (Box 21)
      - Negotiations (S-W), 1995 (Box 22)
      - Negotiations (A-P), 1996 (Box 23)
      - Negotiations (S-W), 1996 (Box 24)
  - Election Files
    - General Election, 1995 (Box 25)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1995-1998; 3185-012; 25.00 cubic feet 25 boxes
  Correspondence, disputes and grievances, negotiations, chronological files, minutes, reports, convention files, newsletters, subject files; 1995-1998 (bulk 1997-1998).
  Received from OPEIU #8, May 26, 2005.
  - Correspondence
    - A-Misc, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Group Health, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Pension Trust-ULP, 1997 (Box 3)
    - VMC-Willapa, 1997 (Box 4)
    - A-GHC, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Homecare-SHA, 1998 (Box 6)
    - SEIU #6-Willapa, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Western States Pension Plan, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - International, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Puget Sound Benefit Trust Correspondence, 1997-1998; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Supplemental Pension Correspondence, 1997-1998; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Minutes
    - International, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Puget Sound Benefit Trust, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Reports
    - International, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Puget Sound Benefit Trust, 1997; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Puget Sound Benefit Trust Reports, 1997; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Chronological Files
    - Maureen Bo, 1997-1998; 8 folders (Box 9)
    - Cindy Schu, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Suzanne Mode, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Phyllis Naiad, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Ligia Farfan, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Ron Weigelt, 1997; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Ron Weigelt, 1997-1998; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - David Winders, 1997-1998; 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Newsletters: Local 8 Journal, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Subject Files
    - Local 8 Miscellaneous, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Silent Auction, 1997; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Voice of the Electorate, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Convention Files
    - Washington State Labor Council Convention – Spokane, WA, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Washington State Labor Council, Committee on Political Education Convention – Seattle, WA, 1998 (Box 10)
    - International Convention – Chicago, IL, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Disputes and Grievances
    - A-C, 1997 (Box 11)
    - H-Mc, 1997 (Box 12)
    - Me-Z, 1997 (Box 13)
    - A-Ba, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Ba-Fl, 1998 (Box 15)
    - Fl-R, 1998 (Box 16)
    - S-Z, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Negotiations
    - DASAS-N, 1995 (Box 18)
    - A-D, 1997 (Box 19)
    - F-SHA, 1997 (Box 20)
    - SHA Group 2, 1997 (Box 21)
    - SEIU-W, 1997 (Box 22)
    - A-W, 1998 (Box 23)
    - SEA MAR, 1998 (Box 24)
    - SHA Group 1 and Master, 1998 (Box 25)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 Records, 1999-2000; 3185-013; 27 cubic feet 27 boxes
  Negotiations, Disputes & Grievances, General Correspondence, "Top Drawer", International correspondence/supplemental pension/western states/PSBT, FPA & SEAMAR notes, 1999-2000.
  Donor: Libby Alejandro, OPEIU #8, November 4, 2007.
  - Negotiations (A - U), 1999 (Box 1)
  - Negotiations (V - Web), GHC 1 of 3, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Negotiations (Wel - Wor), GHC 2 of 3, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Negotiations, GHC 3 of 3, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Disputes & Grievances (A - Bargaining Unit), 1999 (Box 5)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Bej - K), 1999 (Box 6)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Lak - Z), 1999 (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence (A - GHC [Jan-June]), 1999 (Box 8)
  - General Correspondence (GHC [July-Dec] - S), 1999 (Box 9)
  - General Correspondence (S - T), 1999 (Box 10)
  - General Correspondence (T -), 1999 (Box 11)
  - Top Drawer, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Int'l Correspondence/ Supplemental Pension/ Western States/ PSBT, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Negotiations (A - P), 2000 (Box 14)
  - Negotiations (S), 2000 (Box 15)
  - Negotiations (T - W), 2000 (Box 16)
  - FPA & SEAMAR NOTES (CS), 2000 (Box 17)
  - Disputes & Grievances (A - Boo), 2000 (Box 18)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Bri - Hat), 2000 (Box 19)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Her - L), 2000 (Box 20)
  - Disputes & Grievances (M - W), 2000 (Box 21)
  - General Correspondence (A - GHC [Jan-April]), 2000 (Box 22)
  - General Correspondence (GHC [May-Dec] - O), 2000 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence (P - S), 2000 (Box 24)
  - General Correspondence (T - W), 2000 (Box 25)
  - Top Drawer (chron file), 2000 (Box 26)
  - Int'l Correspondence/ Supplemental Pension/ Western States/ PSBT, 2000 (Box 27)
- Office and Professional Employees International union, Local 8 Records, 1995-2004; 3185-014; 55 cubic feet 55 boxes
  Correspondence, disputes and greivances, and contract negotiations.
  Received from Cythia Schu, 4/20/2012
  Open to all users, but access to some parts restricted until 2050
  - General Correspondence [A-GHC], 2001 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence [GHC (May-Oct)], 2001 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence [GHC (Nov-Dec) - Pension Trust], 2001 (Box 3)
  - General Correspondence [PEMC-SMCHC (Jan-Aug)], 2001 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence [SMCHC (Sept-Dec) - T], 2001 (Box 5)
  - General Correspondence [U - W], 2001 (Box 6)
  - Top & Bottom Drawer (Convention/Int'l Correspondence/Pensions/PSBT), 2001 (Box 7)
  - Disputes & Grievances (A-C), 2001 (Box 8)
  - Disputes & Grievances (D-K), 2001 (Box 9)
  - Disputes & Grievances (L-P), 2001 (Box 10)
  - Disputes & Grievances (R-Y), 2001 (Box 11)
  - Negotiations (A - Lathers 1144), 2001 (Box 12)
  - Negotiations (M-P), 2001 (Box 13)
  - Negotiation (S-W), 2001 (Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [A-GHC (Jan-Mar)], 2002 (Box 15)
  - General Correspondence [GHC (Apr-Dec)], 2002 (Box 16)
  - General Correspondence [IFPTE 17- Sea Mar Care Center], 2002 (Box 17)
  - General Correspondence (Sea Mar Clinics – SHA), 2002 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence (SEIU 6 – W), 2002 (Box 19)
  - Top & Bottom Drawer (Convention/Int’l Correspondence/Pensions/PSBT), 2002 (Box 20)
  - Disputes & Grievances (A – E), 2002 (Box 21)
  - Disputes & Grievances (F – Kjo), 2002 (Box 22)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Kh – R), 2002 (Box 23)
  - Disputes & Grievances (S – W), 2002 (Box 24)
  - Negotiations (A – CAMP 1 & 2), 2002 (Box 25)
  - Negotiations (CAMP 3 & 4 – FPA), 2002 (Box 26)
  - Negotiations (GHC [Kelsey Creek Closure] – T), 2002 (Box 27)
  - Negotiations (GHC [Kelsey Creek Closure] – T), 2002 (Box 28)
  - Negotiations (SMCHC), 2002 (Box 29)
  - Negotiations (U – W), 2002 (Box 30)
  - General Correspondence (GHC [June-Dec] – L), 2003 (Box 31)
  - General Correspondence (M – Sea Mar [Jan-June]), 2003 (Box 32)
  - General Correspondence (Sea Mar [July-Dec] – T), 2003 (Box 33)
  - General Correspondence (U – W), 2003 (Box 34)
  - Top & Bottom Drawer (Convention/Int’l Correspondence/Pensions/PSBT), 2003 (Box 35)
  - Disputes & Grievances (A – Doyle), 2003 (Box 36)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Doyle – I), 2003 (Box 37)
  - Disputes & Grievances (J – R), 2003 (Box 38)
  - Disputes & Grievances (S – T), 2003 (Box 39)
  - Disputes & Grievances ([V – Z 2003] AND [A – B 2004]), 2003-2004 (Box 40)
  - Negotiations (A – O), 2003 (Box 41)
  - Negotiations (P – U), 2003 (Box 42)
  - Negotiations (PEMC), 2003 (Box 43)
  - Negotiations (V –W), 2003 (Box 44)
  - General Correspondence (A- GHC [Jan – Oct]), 2004 (Box 45)
  - General Correspondence (GHC [Nov – Dec] – PEMC [1st – 3rd Qtr]), 2004 (Box 46)
  - General Correspondence (PEMC [4th Qtr] – S), 2004 (Box 47)
  - General Correspondence (T – W), 2004 (Box 48)
  - Top & Bottom Drawer (Convention/Int’l Correspondence/Pensions/PSBT), 2004 (Box 49)
  - Disputes & Grievances (C – Kib), 2004 (Box 50)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Kin – Rea), 2004 (Box 51)
  - Disputes & Grievances (Rho – Z), 2004 (Box 52)
  - Negotiations (A – LCCAC), 2004 (Box 53)
  - Negotiations (LIHI – W), 2004 (Box 54)
  - Negotiations/Correspondence IAM 751: 1996-1998; IUOE Local 302: 1996; WACONI: 1995; UFCW Local 21: 1996; Negotiations (DASAS 2000); Negotiations (Sea Mar Care Center 2000), 1995-2000 (Box 55)
- Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 8 records, 2005- 2007; 3185-015; 28.73 cubic feet 26 boxes
  Correspondence, disputes and greivances, and negotiations.
  Access to portions of the collection is restricted. Contact University of Washington Libraries Special Collections for details.
  Libby Alejandro, OPEIU Local 8 and Cindy Shiu, OPEIU Local 8, 2015
  - Series 1: General Correspondence, 2005-2007
    - General Correspondence (A – GHC [Jan-Nov]), 2005 (Box 1)
    - General Correspondence (GHC [Dec]-P), 2005 (Box 2)
    - General Correspondence (S-W), 2005 (Box 3)
    - General Correspondence (W-GH [Jan-May 2006]), 2005-2006 (Box 4)
    - General Correspondence (GH [June-December]-O), 2006 (Box 5)
    - General Correspondence (P-Seattle Housing Authority [2nd Qtr], 2006 (Box 6)